http://carltonstraining.com/privacy-policy/

CARLTON'S TRAINING SOLUTIONS PRIVACY POLICY
Carlton's Training Solutions takes your privacy very seriously.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how Jim Case and Carlton's Training treats personal information that Carlton's Training collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Carlton's Training products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, company, address, email address, or phone number, and purchase history with our company.
Information Collection and Use
When you purchase items from our website, Jim Case personally, Jack Cash, or via email we ask for information such as your name, company, email address, zip code, and industry. Carlton's Training collects information about your transactions with us Carlton's Training uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, and to contact you regarding your orders.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Carlton's Training is owned by Jack Cash and does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you.
Browse by Authors
John CleeseBen ZanderBob FarrellDewitt JonesJoel BarkerKen BlanchardLou HoltzMorris MasseyTom Peters
Browse by Topics
Interviewing and HiringLeadershipBest SellersConflict ResolutionCustomer ServiceDiversity TrainingChange ManagementInnovationHarassment TrainingFinance TrainingEthics/ValuesCommunication TrainingCoachingLegal IssuesManagementMeeting OpenersMotivationalGenerational IssuesPerformance AppraisalPerformance ManagementSales Training Sexual HarassmentTeam BuildingTelephone Customer ServiceTime ManagementTrain the TrainerWorkplace ViolenceMuppet Meeting OpenersSubstance AbuseBiological ThreatsSafetyCatherine CrierJames AutryJoe Torre & Lou HoltzJohn KotterHealthcare Training VideosMeetingsWorkplace BullyingHospitality Training Videos
Compare Products
You have no items to compare.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Thank you for your subscribing.
Be alerted to sales and end of year and quaterly specials:
View Larger Map
LOCATION
11693 San Vicente Blvd,
email response hourly for questions,
and emergency orders.
